foreign
[Music]
but I didn't put these chickens here
and also I got about 10
000 comments telling me that oh wait I
totally am a detective
I got 10 000 comments and that's no
exaggeration telling me that Mumbo did
not build something in my base did not
he he definitely 100 did not build
something in my base at the same time as
those messages came pouring in
these guys started appearing now at
first I was just like oh my poetry man
must have just left a few here yeah why
would he do that I'll just have to get
released and I've been I've just been
hitting these guys and getting rid of
them as they appear
but then I realized
they keep coming back
so clearly someone and I don't know who
has built something in my base that is
releasing chickens periodically
and I am going to get to the bottom of
this and
is that lava oh boy
okay wait oh whoa whoa
someone has left me some signage rise
and shine Mr Green rise and shine not
that I dream to insinuate that you've
been sleeping on watch no one is more
deserving of a break than what on Earth
the right make a difference Mr wake up
and smell prank prank war prank will
never oh come on
what the heck is all this stuff at Joe
Hills this has got to be Joe I'm sorry I
know Joe well enough now that this has
got to be him he's the only one that
would use some sort of War speech or
something to to get me back but I'm not
entirely sure what all of this is about
and he clearly broke a creeper up here
as well you know what I think I'm just
gonna I'm just gonna ask him straight up
you know what there's too much there's
too much stuff going on in this Prank
War for me to have another enemy this
needs to be sorted out right now today
hello Joe
and I'll agreeing am I right in assuming
that you wrote me some sort of Novel and
left a bit of uh Lighting on my base
[Laughter]
especially due to the lack of light well
I I think there's definitely been some
sort of miscommunication here so you're
this is a retaliation because I swooped
in and made your literature prank rather
lethal is that is that right am I
understanding this correctly well it's
not maybe a literature prank as much as
a ethics lesson morality oh so you're
literally teaching him a lesson oh this
is I I don't know if I could let this
slide Joe this is like this is like old
school this is old school pouring lava
on a base well I am one of the old as
the kids say being over 30 years old but
you know what that also means I keep
coupons I've got one coupon here for an
IOU from Korean that you gave me for my
uh wishing well like eight months ago or
something I was wondering because I took
so much paper for some reason I don't
even remember why I thought maybe we can
kind of find a way to overlook this
miscommunication involving lava and
science on both sides oh my goodness I
never thought that this IOU would
actually come back to haunt me so you
want me to owe you uh a truce or a piece
or something
I I want you to owe me forgiveness and
understanding that's all I've I've
really only wanted Mutual understanding
so we'll throw in forgiveness on top of
that and then we'll call it a day okay
that seems favorite all right uh I never
I never thought that this would actually
come back and haunt me okay I I will
accept that I can I'll bury what did he
say we'll bury the hatch is that what
you say yes we'll bury the Hatcher so it
took a little while for all the lava to
make its way down the bottom but all of
a sudden It sped up and it took quite a
while but no damage done really as soon
as those blocks were taken care of the
rest just drained away so it looked way
worse than it actually was no harm no
foul well I'm glad we sorted that out
because I cannot be dealing with another
enemy just like iskau did let's get rid
of these we don't need these these
snowballs anymore what a waste of time
there's no time for friendly snowball
fights when there's a friendly prank war
going on you know I need to create a war
room which is why I've got one of of
each hermit's head oh here we go green
we need your attention immediately is it
is it that important I'm in the middle
of something I don't really use the
inside of here so why don't I use this
to create the temporary wall so I can
know who's on my side and who isn't now
all we're gonna do is label who we
consider an ally and who we consider an
enemy impulse definitely on this side
because he was part of the Ghost Ship
iskal iskal uh friend I'd say zombie
Clio definitely friend Ren definitely
enemy X he was siding with Doc that
lean's Doc is there as well man we're
outnumbered at the moment
false ah see that false is confusing
because I helped her with the prank but
then she went against Ren no she went
against iskau false is a difficult one
because I don't have any problem with
her directly so she's somewhere in the
middle for me stress I don't know Mumbo
don't know
scar don't know me I'm on this side
Tango is definitely on my side he helped
me with the heist Joe is on my side as
well I think because he's allied with
Cleo even though he did prank me I guess
he's now on this side
so that leaves stress scar Mumbo and
false to work out where they are but
there is um quite clearly two sides
forming here anyway iskal needs our help
with something rather urgently I what
else is here
rocket sail one diamond for four stacks
absolute bargain so what did they say
exactly can you come and meet me and
stress at the chicken coop okay hello
hello hello hello what's going on
um well well you break okay you break
the news stress
some
some happened to to Sally but it's so
far
who's Sally
I don't have a chicken
yeah chicken Sally no I don't have a
chicken
I'm pretty sure you do it's over there
look you built it looks pretty
um wasn't me
totally was you it wasn't but it wasn't
me I don't I don't own a chicken so but
you built it and everything
I don't remember that
you don't remember building a cherry
blossom I mean it clearly says here
liberated by poultry man it was not me
it was the man in the chicken costume
how many times do I have to say this why
does everyone keep blaming me for what
the man in the chicken costume does it's
ridiculous
you know what I'll just go and get him
guys I think they might be on to me I I
don't I don't want to arouse any
suspicion
but I think they might know portugu
man's true identity
they were just guessing they were just
they've been calling everyone poetry man
I'm sure of it
I'll look korean's back good no
it's it's me
the the superhero uh I was told that
there was a disturbance
you agreeing like the your your chicken
salad she got taken
um into a dungeon what do you mean by
dog why like
I'm acted because it's diamonds but
she's right here she's right here
um yeah We rescued her we were yeah
wrestled with her quotations yes yeah we
were Heroes We Were Your Heroes
are you saying that I'm not a good hero
uh even heroes need oh listen even
heroes needs uh other people to hear all
them when they are sleeping or yeah have
a have a few eggs here
basically what happened was that doc
abducted your chicken and put her in a
dungeon and we were Hills we went let me
show you let me show you come over here
how do you do that how did he do that
part of my magic superpower how did he
do that
no wait how did he do that I just
watched you perform impossible Minecraft
hacks yeah down here after after many
hours of searching we found this
horrible place okay down here check this
out
okay going after you Green Oh yeah and
Sally was prisoned imprisoned in here
this looks better than the plot that I
made her to be fair
looks like the poultry cave it's nice so
we were Heroes and We rescued her from
this room that puffer fish did not
killer no no
face was here and even puffer fish was
here yes
saved her we saved her yeah yeah
I
I should have been there this is
unacceptable I'm gonna have to give up
my title as the best superhero on This
Server oh no don't be silly don't be
silly you are still the bestest
superheroes of all superhero ever you're
the only they write stories about you
headline
Pokemon strikes again I read it this
morning you guys I think I'm a good
superhero
it's a busy life
it's a busy life we understand that we
got your back so there's a new Sally now
well no she's well she's she's a little
tiny bit brand new
um but the Sally's still there it's all
good that's okay there's lots of new
chickens there's more chickens where
that came from
chickens come and go dude it's okay oh
look Sally's a mother now
oh
say yeah yeah but since she survives the
age cycle because otherwise should we do
that
yeah yeah yeah do the danger
oh no okay we're gonna age her
yay
she died
no
are you kidding me
oh no what is that but she's still here
she's still right here but she's still
here yeah the repression's coming up
there yeah
I'm sorry I'm so confused they're so
confused I'm sorry your mommy died no
well thanks for saving Sally even if it
wasn't meant to be I appreciate that
but I think I think my my job here is
done
okay
man
oh look I agreeing he's back already
already Grant like I was just uh I've
just been informals going on ah sad sad
news because you're chicken I mean
Porter man's chicken is dead
this is really sad oh that is sad huh oh
well
um so there is a serious problem on This
Server guys
serious problem last time I saw you with
gal you had like a a wall of of heads
I've also made a wall of heads
and you are on my good side at the
moment and then there's a few people
that are like sitting in the middle for
me maybe we should like
convene and work out who's who's on both
of our sides
that would be very helpful because I
tried to do that earlier today and it is
so confusing it is really confusing
oh okay you've got jevin on this side I
didn't put Evan on my side yet
yeah I'm see I'm not I'm not entirely
sure like I said I'm very confused
but this is what I figured out so far
oh okay we've got slightly different
walls going on so we might need to if
we're on the same team we need to work
out who's an ally and who's not you go
ahead I assume stress isn't on the other
side seeing as she's right here
yay
so she's on the side again of us Mumbo
he's done nothing zaf nothing Cub
nothing python nothing scar nothing and
two four Chef nothing now see I actually
saw Joe earlier and we uh apologize to
each other and fixed our differences so
he's either in the middle or he's on our
side I have false in the middle at the
moment because I haven't actually done
anything with her apart from the the
prank on Ren
if I'm on your side you have to protect
your peers because she she I I pranked
her you blew up her cake oh yeah she
took pride in that bird poop cake yeah
actually yeah you're right okay so we
really need to meet up with our guys
that because they don't even know like
Tango jevin Cleo they don't know we've
done this they don't know that we're
allies well I guess they do but they
don't know like officially we need to
like meet up with everybody
I agree because like what if they are
not happy with the like they may be I
yeah maybe they might have a different
they ever might have a different set of
walls maybe mumbo's on that side I don't
know you uh talk to my people and my
people yeah your people talk to my
people but I'll talk to my cat and see
what he says about all this yeah they
can talk to stress's cat and then we can
go from there yeah definitely and my
dogs will will bark yeah okay that
sounds good that makes perfect sense
just just like this server
yes
now my wool seems a little bit outdated
but it's all coming together and the
team has been notified I've messaged
everybody so hopefully we'll be able to
get together fairly soon in the next
couple of days to work out our plan of
action because things are getting pretty
serious now we are all having quite a
good time actually it's actually been a
really really fun experience anyway
there's not any more chickens uh coming
out but I keep periodically hearing
something and I'm pretty sure there's a
mechanism here so what I'm gonna do is
I'm just gonna AFK in this general
direction I don't know exactly where
because the chickens are all centered or
were centered around there I've now
gotten rid of all of them but I'm pretty
sure if I just wait long enough uh Mumbo
or whoever it was built something around
this area so I'm pretty sure if we just
wait long enough we'll see where it
where it is
oh there it is there there it was I saw
it okay that took about four minutes it
was over here somewhere
I think
no
uh-huh absolutely rumbled
now what has he created here
oh my goodness this is
complicated so if I'm understanding this
there's a timer here full of junk and
then that passes into another Hopper
down there which then triggers all of
these Pistons to release but it's it's
got no eggs left that's why yeah amateur
mistake Mumbo you need to fill it up
with chickens to be constantly laying
eggs to fuel this fire but what a little
ingenious little system here
so it turns out Mumbo did build
something in my base
who would have saw that coming not me
[Laughter]
just as I say that off it goes well I
think all we need to do here is just
remove this
and that's all we need to do and it will
not bother us anymore anyway I want to
continue building a little bit in my
base because I've been working on the
ring that runs all the way around and
I've got a new design that I want to put
in it and see what you guys think
so I've put my camera account at the top
of my base facing down so I've got this
really cool angle even if you can't see
absolutely everything so this pattern is
fairly simple now you might be wondering
why am I now deleting all of those white
concrete blocks that I spent hours
placing the first time that I made this
and that's pretty simple I had no idea
what pattern I wanted on this giant
Circle but now I think I do and it looks
pretty cool and actually it was seeing
the map on iskal's war room that made me
think oh actually it could use some sort
of pattern there that was a bit bigger
so all in all it was fairly simple I
just leave one block Gap either side of
this giant Circle delete the inside and
replace it with some cyan glass now I've
actually got loads of these materials
lying around loads of glass loads of
sand because I've just grinded all that
out for hours and hours but actually
recuperating all of this white concrete
means that all of this can now go go
into producing the wall underwater now I
am slightly under estimating exactly how
much work was involved because this took
well over an hour and I didn't expect
that I thought I could do this in about
half an hour but no it took a long time
and the underside the big wall that's
going to have to go around is also going
to take hours and hours and hours so I'm
gonna have to break up this project over
time but I really want to finish this
base sometime soon I unfortunately did
not have time to finish the entire thing
but I think it actually looks really
really cool if you imagine that all the
way around it looks like a proper
Crosshair now I know it looks a little
bit thin and it it doesn't load properly
half the time but it actually looks like
pools of water inside it now I think
that once this whole thing is fish
because down under here there's no wall
and I think that doesn't help the matter
but around here I've started creating
more of a finished product as you can
see this is a really big project there's
a lot of resources going into this now
I'm just not sure what to do with the
giant bottle because this wall basically
slices right through it and this is
where we started guys it might seem like
a long time ago now all those months ago
we started in this shipwreck in a bottle
but I didn't want to get rid of this I
mean it's even got some mistakes still
in there I don't want to get rid of it
so I might have to do some sort of thing
to make an arch over the top I don't
really want to cover it up or slice
through it in any way
anyway I think that's it from me
everyone next episode I really want to
experiment with my Towers a bit more now
I know I did the only experiment thing
I've done are these little details here
but I think that I can do something a
little bit better I've just been really
hesitant because there's a fine delicacy
about this it's almost it's almost
because this is really simple
thank you
I think that there's a beauty and
simplicity in this sort of uh build here
and I don't want to over complicate it
however there is still stuff missing and
I think that pattern has actually
improved it quite a lot especially once
it goes all the way around it'll look
really cool on the map from the top down
however there's still so much that needs
doing maybe even cool bridges that go
inside that oh that might look cool as
well there's a lot that can be done here
and I'm not going to give up working and
perfecting this entire base not to
mention trying to fill up the inside of
this anyway
thank you very much for watching
everyone that is unfortunately all we
have time for today however next episode
there's a lot going on there's a lot
going on so I look forward to making
that and I'll see you guys in the next
video goodbye